<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog/Reflections on nowlin.io</title><link>http://localhost:1313/unt-mls/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Blog/Reflections on nowlin.io</description><image><title>nowlin.io</title><url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url><link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:23:26 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/unt-mls/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2023Fall</title><link>http://localhost:1313/unt-mls/posts/2023fall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:23:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/unt-mls/posts/2023fall/</guid><description>Blog Post #2: Fall 2023 Reflections note: This was an assigned task for INFO 5000 originally submitted November 7, 2023
Semester Number Two: The Grind I am in the midst of my second semester in UNT&amp;rsquo;s MLS program. In my first semester, I took Management of Information Agencies (INFO 5300), Public Libraries (INFO 5320), and Information Access and Knowledge Inquiry (INFO 5600). That courseload, taken during the Spring 2023 semester, was enlightening regarding graduate-level preparations and submissions, big-picture considerations as far as the profession and my trajectory are concerned, and the information learned.</description></item><item><title>2023Spring</title><link>http://localhost:1313/unt-mls/posts/2023spring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:23:18 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/unt-mls/posts/2023spring/</guid><description>Blog Post #1: Spring 2023 Reflections note: This was an assigned task, submitted for INFO 5600 originally submitted May 1, 2023
Reading Reflections of INFO 5600 Reference professionals help disseminate accurate and reliable information to inquring users. Information services in libraries serve the purpose of sharing information with inquiring users. There are many ways users can acquire information, and a simple Google search may satisfy their needs. Information professionals need to add a dose of customer service and expertise to separate libraries from web-crawling search engines.</description></item></channel></rss>